codeforbanks.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - codeforbanks.com

As a user of www.codeforbanks.com website, you must agree to have read our privacy policy before sharing any personal information with us. We respect your privacy. Codeforbanks does not collect any personal information from its users. Visits are logged for aggregate statistics and diagnosis. The visitors are free to navigate through our website without providing any personal information. We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

## __Links To Other Websites

Our website contains links to other sites. The users need to take notice of the fact that we are not responsible if you are asked to submit your personal information on the linked site. We advise users to go through the privacy policy of the linked sites before sharing any information with the same.

## __Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with these ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information.

## __Cookies

Our website uses cookies like other websites. Kindly be informed that at certain places of the website, we make use of cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

## __Social Website Cookies

In our website cookies are used by social websites (like Facebook and Twitter) so you can easily Like or Share our contents with the respective sharing buttons on our site. The privacy implications on this will vary from the different social websites and are dependent on the privacy settings you have chosen on these networks. 

## __Advertising Cookies

Cookies are widely used in online advertising. We or our advertising partner do not gain personally identifiable information from these cookies. We also use Google Ads on our site, and these ads might place a DoubleClick DART cookie please do note that the following info regarding the cookie placed via ads served via google. 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
